sunslocker.com 2011-03-15

# Phoenix Suns NBA News - Suns Basketball Blog » Privacy Policy

## SunsLocker.com Privacy Policy

SunsLocker.com values the privacy of our visitors and our members and takes many steps to protect their privacy. By visiting SunsLocker.com’s primary website or related websites that SunsLocker.com controls or operates (collectively “SunsLocker.com Sites”), or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement. 

### What this Privacy Statement Covers

This Privacy Statement covers SunsLocker.com’s treatment of personally identifiable information (”Personal Information”) that SunsLocker.com gathers when you access SunsLocker.com Sites. This Privacy Statement does not apply to the use of your Personal Information by third parties that SunsLocker.com does not own or control, or to individuals that SunsLocker.com does not control or manage. 

### Links to Other Sites

SunsLocker.com Sites contains links to blogs and other websites that are not owned or controlled by SunsLocker.com. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites. 

### Information Collection & Use

SunsLocker.com is the sole owner of information collected on SunsLocker.com Sites. We do not share or sell your information with anyone without your authorization or consent in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Statement. 

### Registration

SunsLocker.com provides some features exclusively to its members. Our registration process requires you to provide SunsLocker.com with a valid email address as well as a username and password of your choice. Optional information such as your first and last name, year of birth, zip code, and country of residence helps SunsLocker.com have a better understanding of its visitors and members. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of special features offered only to our members. 

### Minor’s Privacy

We do not collect or maintain information on SunsLocker.com Sites from those people we actually know are under 13 years old, and no part of any SunsLocker.com Site is structured to attract anyone under 13 years old. 

### Surveys or Contests

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on SunsLocker.com Sites. If you participate we will request certain Personal Information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). 

We only use this information internally to determine eligibility, notify contest winners, and to measure the success of our efforts. 

## Communications from SunsLocker.com Sites

### Newsletters

By registering at any of SunsLocker.com’s sites, you choose to subscribe to our newsletter(s). We will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Unsubscribe instructions accompany each email. 

### Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on the rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if SunsLocker.com is acquired or lava from an erupting volcano swallows our data center we might notify you with an e-mail.  
You may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive these announcements you have the option to deactivate your account. 

### Customer Service

Based upon the Personal Information you provide us we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or by telephone in accordance with your wishes. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information about our visitors and the world of weblogs in general with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual visitors or members. We do not link aggregate visitor or member data with Personal Information. 

We may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples of such services include sending email, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. 

We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to (1) comply with the law; (2) enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; (3) or protect the rights, property or safety of SunsLocker.com, our employees, our users, or others. 

### Security and Confidentiality

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

### Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to access and edit all of your Personal Information within our member profile page or by using our Customer Support contact form. Information collected for the membership process, if requested, will be deleted within 21 days from the SunsLocker.com Sites. However, some Personal Information may need to be maintained if it is connected with billing information or as required by law. 

Users of the SunsLocker.com Sites are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party. 

You may opt-out of receiving our newsletter by following the instructions included in each newsletter or by contacting us. 

We gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, requested pages, operating system, and the time and date your browser requested our pages. We use this information, which does not identify individual visitors, to analyze trends, to administer the SunsLocker.com Sites, to track visitor movements around the SunsLocker.com Sites and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this collected data to Personal Information.

### Cookies

We store a small text file called a cookie on your computer to track session data and persist your login for your convenience. A session cookie expires when you exit your browser. A persistent cookie stays on your computer until it is deleted. You can remove persistent cookies by following the directions provided in your browser’s “help” files. 

If you reject cookies you may still use the SunsLocker.com Sites. 

Some of our advertisers may use cookies on the SunsLocker.com Sites. We have no access or control over these cookies. This Privacy Statement covers the use of cookies by SunsLocker.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

### Third Party Advertisers

The advertisements appearing on SunsLocker.com are delivered by a third party. For information about our advertising partner, please visit their website through the link included in the presentation of the advertisements on the SunsLocker.com Sites. 

### Business Transitions

In the event SunsLocker.com goes through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of SunsLocker.com may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Statement. You hereby consent to SunsLocker.com sharing your Personal Information under the above circumstances. SunsLocker.com will contact you at the email address you provided at registration to communicate such transfer. We will also place a prominent notice on the SunsLocker.com home page for 30 days after such transfer of your Personal Information. 

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

This Privacy Statement is a living document. We will modify this document as we add new features to SunsLocker.com Sites. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time. If we make material changes to our privacy policy we will post those changes to this Privacy Statement, the SunsLocker.com.com homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy please contact us.
